{
    "_id": "1",
    "name": "State Capitals",
    "description": "The capitals of all 50 states in the U.S.",
    "creation_date": "1559404138",
    "tags": [
        "Geography", "US", "Trivia"
    ],
    "card_count": "13",
    "cards": [{
        "prompt": "Alabama",
        "answer": "Montgomery"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Alaska",
        "answer": "Juneau"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Arizona",
        "answer": "Phoenix"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Arkansas",
        "answer": "Little Rock"
    }, {
        "prompt": "California",
        "answer": "Sacramento"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Colorado",
        "answer": "Denver"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Connecticut",
        "answer": "Hartford"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Delaware",
        "answer": "Dover"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Florida",
        "answer": "Tallahassee"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Georgia",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Hawaii",
        "answer": "Honolulu"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Idaho",
        "answer": "Boise"
    }, {
        "prompt": "Illinois",
        "answer": "Springfield"
    }]
}
